{
    "id": "0ea888de2f404978a3b8606e2474b252",
    "title": "Noun clause exercise",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "be9a0d607db54d168d30d4ab0fc2ce26",
            "title": "Noun Clause",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "I often wonder ............................ he is getting on.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "what",
                        "how",
                        "that"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I want to know ..................................... she is angry with me.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "that",
                        "why"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "He asked me ................................... I knew his name.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "if",
                        "that",
                        "unless"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "She said ........................................... she would not come.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "if",
                        "that",
                        "whether"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I feel .................................. I will fail.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "that",
                        "what"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I thought .................................... she would arrive.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "that",
                        "what"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "...................................... you should cheat me hurts me.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "What",
                        "That",
                        "Why"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I don’t know ................................... I can get out of this mess.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "that",
                        "how"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I don’t know ...................................... he wants.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "that",
                        "what",
                        "if"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I went to see ..................................... had happened.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "how",
                        "that",
                        "what"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "Pay careful attention to ..................................... I am going to say.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "that",
                        "what",
                        "how"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "She told me ................................... she would be delighted to come.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "as",
                        "that"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}